MY BELOVED DEMON
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
It hurts, right?
To To Hee.
Your heart is about to break in two.
Like a ripe apple.
See you in hell.
Director Chong!
Director Chon.
That scoundrel!
- Director Chon.
- Someone fell.
Call an ambulance!
Please bring To To Hee!
Bring on To To Hee!
To To Hee!
I know better than anyone
that it is not your fault, Mrs. To.
But the management put pressure on me.
When will I be released?
You will be able to leave when the warrant is processed.
It will be rejected because there is no evidence.
Detective Puck.
- What is it?
- Thing...
Pressure and pulse decrease.
More liquids, please.
He'll be fine, right?
Please save him.
Please let me see you.
He was stabbed!
He is dying as we speak.
Please?
Sok Hune.
I have to get out of here.
I have to see Jung Koo Won.
I have to see him.
More bandages, please.
Dropper to the maximum.
Ready for surgery?
Yes, everyone is waiting.
Take the patient to the operating room…
Please save him.
Hang in there Jung Ku Won.
A little more.
OPERATIONAL
How is he, doctor?
We sewed up the wound
but he had already lost too much blood.
And his heart valves are seriously damaged.
He may not live to see the morning.
Do something.
Do whatever it takes to save him!
Please save him.
I am begging you.
- Quickly.
- It's your fault.
All this happened because of you.
You killed Principal Chong!
- Let go!
- Godi.
get yourself together
We have to save Director Chong first.
Come with me.
Please wait outside the door.
It's too late.
I was late.
You were always there and protected me.
And I...
couldn't...
you are heavy Will you move?
Jung Ku Won.
Close up of your tearful face
very funny
It's so funny that I can't even die.
I thought you died!
Are you not fully healed?
Only half worked again.
Futile forces.
I will bring a doctor.
Just give me a minute.
I need to recharge.
Director Jon…
She saved him.
she doesn't know
how it will threaten her life.
poor thing
EPISODE 8
FATEFUL CHOICE
To Hee
I will be back soon.
I won't leave you for too long.
Star Chin.
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Still
I was satisfied
to be a person who is always there
with Director Chong.
Because I was more special than other people.
There was no other woman besides me.
And then she appeared.
To To Hee…
became more important than me.
Why don't you ask anything?
Because you won't tell me anyway.
Thank you.
You don't have to say that to me.
Like "thank you" or "sorry".
i have enough
that you are safe
That's all I need.
Let's hurry up. Not worth it
causing trouble for Detective Puck.
To To Hee.
Hasn't he gotten up yet?
But the doctor said
that he now has to improve.
Why does he not recover?
What is happening to him at all?
Well…
How is Mr. Chong?
Still in critical condition.
Director Chon.
Director Chong!
is everything ok
Does it hurt so much?
Just…
I had a terrible dream.
Director Chon.
It hurts.
Sorry.
Where To To Hee?
The result should already be announced.
Detective Puck.
What this time?
The order was reviewed and...
he was rejected.
Why did you pause?
You scared me.
How is Jung Koo Won?
Came to my senses.
What a relief.
STATIONARY HOSPITAL
HANKUK UNIVERSITY
Bring me some water, Mr. Puck.
Do you want water?
Not this one.
I want cold water.
You want cold water.
Kryzhanoy
Well, because where's my straw
You can sit down.
What is that?
I know how much you love sweets.
I tasted them and they melt in my mouth.
sit down
OK.
scratch my back Madly itching.
- A little higher.
- Here?
- A little lower.
- Somewhere here?
Are you deliberately not scratching there?
why did you stop
In a past life, you were definitely a nobleman.
It is very natural for you to manage others.
- Somewhere here?
- No.
Yes, that's it.
You can sit down.
Maybe I look normal on the outside
and inside I'm in a terrible state.
How is your recovery going?
I think I almost played the box.
It's a miracle you survived.
I thought I would never see you again.
What are you talking about? I am a demon.
I am an apex predator…
Press the button for pain relief.
For pain relief...
Insanely painful.
- What are you doing?
- I pressed her.
Continue
- But...
- More.
Continue
To To Hee?
Delivery.
- Delivery?
- What is it?
Here.
Put them here.
GET OVER SOON BOSS
WILD DOGS
Goodbye
Do they think this is a ritual bureau?
What a fool
funeral wreaths for a recovering person?
"Wild dogs"?
Who are they?
We have to protect the boss.
- Let's protect him!
sir
boss
- Boss!
What scoundrel did this to you?
Boss, I'll find the bastard and…
I'm not your boss, and I'm not dead yet.
So get rid of the flowers.
Are you hurt, boss?
- Nurse! Doctor!
- Help!
- Bring the director of the hospital!
- Get out!
- Well, because!
- Quickly!
If you get closer,
than five meters,
I will make you regret it.
- Back off.
- And so on.
- Step back a little more.
- God, how far.
That's five meters, sir.
The boss gave the historic first order.
Do not cross this line.
Everyone get out here!
WE BARK FOR LOVE TO THE BOSS
HAW-HAW
What is wrong with them?
It's better to get another blow to the head.
That's for sure.
Disgusting
sir
Guys, the boss's wife has arrived.
- You are beautiful, lady!
Are you the wife of the boss?
Don't look them in the eye.
sir
The bed is too high.
Lying down on it is like climbing a mountain.
- Jeong Ku Won!
- To To Hee!
Can you walk now?
Of course. Everything is fine. look
You can't walk yet.
Go to bed immediately.
It's really all right, I swear.
Of course.
Who are the men in black behind the door?
It just so happened that Director Chong
popular with a variety of people.
Let's go home already.
if i stay here
those scoundrels will bore me.
Your treatment is not yet complete.
The best treatment is to be with you.
Heart pounded.
OK.
Maybe Mr. Chong was showing a temper,
but he had a good heart.
Even those who blamed Ms. To
in murder, support us
hearing what happened to him.
It's because they feel guilty!
What is the point in all this now?
why are you crying
It's not necessary. We have to work.
Let's give Ms. To a nice schedule,
which shows a change in public opinion.
This is the last gift
Mr. Chon Mrs. To!
We have to get back to work!
A little
Mr. Chong is fine.
- Excuse me?
- What?
I knew that!
I chose a good card today!
Really?
Mr. Chong!
He saw my face. He will find me.
Grandpa!
He is approaching.
He will find me.
There is not even a static voltage,
not that sparks.
Maybe we can speed up the charging,
if we touch a larger area of the body.
This is very logical.
Then…
shall we try to hug?
This is a good offer.
Then…
should I do it?
No.
Rather like this.
How about…
How do you like it?
I feel how wonderfully I recharge.
What I won't go to just to charge you.
All this happened because of you.
You killed Principal Chong!
You woke up.
Yes.
Don't move.
Let's go find that scoundrel.
I saw his true face
even half.
And I can find it.
In this state, you will not go anywhere.
The main thing is recovery.
The main thing is revenge.
I will find him and rip his heart out of…
You are not yet ready to take revenge.
Works
Not anymore.
I think you need much more.
But...
It became much easier to breathe.
The more you charge,
then you should be getting better.
I have to go to work.
Can you take a day off?
- No.
- Absolutely not?
But you are the general director.
Will you celebrate my survival
announcing today…
company anniversary?
rest
Then only five more minutes.
Let me recharge a little more.
Yesterday was total chaos.
For world peace
let's make up
We didn't fight, so we have nothing to reconcile.
And I don't care about world peace.
There was once a man who loved to eat pork.
For now, let's call him K.
Somehow
K met a very special pig.
Imagine that K falls in love
into this special pig
and then in all the pigs in the world.
Will K become a vegetarian then?
What do you say?
let's work together
to make K a vegetarian.
What a delusion.
She doesn't seem to understand
that world peace is in our hands.
The demon is about to become a guardian.
wait
Let me go with you.
Do not take the wound lightly.
You almost played the box.
So stay home and rest today.
Look what he did to me.
Who knows what he can do to you?
Another guard is waiting for me in the office.
So don't worry and…
No. Now I'm just
I can't trust anyone.
And if that scoundrel comes
as a bodyguard?
I will protect you myself.
stand up
I forbid you.
Who gave you that right?
As your butler I care first
about your safety.
- You won't protect anyone in such a state.
- Then you are fired.
You are no longer my butler
so don't get up and go home.
You are so frivolous
our capitalist friendship?
Do as he says.
Do as I say.
- I am offended!
- Just a little!
Actually, there is a solution.
This car is quite big.
to accommodate us with plenty.
Am I right?
And you don't have to work on the show
instead of following me?
Let's postpone the show.
how do we go on
if you've just been hurt?
I don't quite see the connection here.
A robot like you will not understand.
You need to recharge
at every opportunity.
You said that it is not possible with others.
Now we are officially married.
At the request of an anonymous person
I blamed Ms. To To Hee
in the assassination of Chairman Choo Jung-suk.
I caused Ms. To To Hee a lot of damage.
I sincerely apologize.
You keep a register of articles
and comments by keywords?
- Yes, sir.
- And one more thing
will come with Mr. Chong
general manager of the Sunvol Foundation.
I wonder if the general manager
as handsome as Mr. Jeon.
Be careful, because you will fall into the mirror.
Here they are.
A man with a twisted head?
Yes, that's him.
Sorry about that day.
You scared me!
- I just...
- Everything is fine.
I wanted to celebrate
Mr. Chong's discharge from the hospital.
Is everyone okay?
After yesterday's confession
"Clickbait news"
and an attack on Mr.…
that is, the attack on Director Chon,
public opinion about Mrs. To
has changed radically.
Favorable comments and articles
the two of you are also being talked about.
Those who accused you of murder
now showing sympathy.
That's right. Now they want to know
who tried to destroy you
and kill Mr. Chong.
Now no one will stop you
to run for the post of chairman.
All thanks to Mr. Chong,
who risked his life for Ms. To.
Applause!
Actually, I made you a cake
but did not submit it earlier,
because the firecracker scared you.
What kind of cake? Strawberry? Chocolate?
Yes, yes.
I don't like green tea and whipped cream.
No, he is not from that.
This is a black tea chiffon cake.
- Really?
- One, two
- One, two, three, four
- Congratulations
- Dear director Chona
- Congratulations, dear Mr. Chong
- Congratulations, dear Mr. Cone
- With an extract
Make a wish?
- Of course.
- Yes.
One, two, three.
Sorry.
is everything ok
- What is it?
- What are you talking about?
Why are you so scared?
I have never seen you before
so scared
Me? Frightened?
I am a demon.
Nice try, but don't fool me.
go back to the theater
if you carry the delusion further.
Then as you wish.
I'll tell To To Hee
so that she had to sit for two.
You won't do that.
Then just tell me what's going on.
I had a dream.
I was engulfed in a huge flame,
my whole body was on fire.
i still feel
as the tips of the fingers burned.
It drives me crazy.
Was it spontaneous combustion?
This is what people call it
fear?
Director Chon.
I think
my mind is weakening along with my strength.
When I recover, everything will be back to normal.
I came to see Director Chong.
Now he is gone.
Then I want to see Ms. To.
Please continue.
Thank you.
Ms. Chin Ka-yong has come to see you.
Would you like coffee or tea?
No need.
I didn't come to chat.
Time to use Director Chon,
time to let him go.
We need each other.
Each other?
That is, you need him.
You lead him by the nose
taking advantage of his weakness.
He almost died because of you.
How selfish will you be?
Deal with your problems yourself.
Time to exploit Director Chon
and threaten him dad.
I watched the video from the theater,
and you were right.
The book was stolen.
An hour of video from security cameras was missing
since the evening of the book's disappearance
and from the day you were attacked.
The attacker installed a virus,
to spoil the video at a certain time.
then he knows
who am i
Mr. Chong
Someone was looking for you earlier.
Who?
A tall woman. I don't know who.
Director Chong!
I am glad to see that you are all right.
Thank God.
I will call a taxi.
Go Mr. Paku.
I want to speak to the director.
About what?
Just go, Star Chin.
I'm not for long.
Chula, your powers are flickering.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine when I get my dad back.
I'm not sure.
The reason why your strength is weakening -
To To Hee.
Everything is wrong.
You want to believe it.
In your heart you know it too.
Everything indicates that the problem is in her.
You can't avoid it.
Is she special to you now?
She sits down
do you have a special place in your heart?
You are becoming more and more human,
because through it you experience human emotions.
Because you...
in love with her
Love is the pinnacle of humanity.
- Stop.
- You have to stop.
If you're a demon, behave yourself!
Didn't you say it yourself
that people are unimportant and weak?
Do you want to become one?
You have to stop.
If you don't stop,
it will not end there.
Want to listen to music?
No, thank you.
Of course.
Did Ka Yeon say something stupid to you?
But no.
She just invited me to her show.
Did she say something to you?
No.
Please come to the show.
While it is postponed, it is not for long.
Swords will whistle in the air.
I will come
It must have shocked Ms. Chin that
what happened to you
I felt how much you care about her.
Ms. Chu.
to me
continue to go forward?
Jung Ku Won almost died because of me
although he is not involved in any way
to this struggle.
I don't know if I should go any further
at the expense of other people.
But...
if i give up here
it will be unfair to you.
Don't worry about the dead.
I'm just worried it's getting to you.
It gets me.
It got to me so much, I'm upset.
I lost my dear family
and I don't even know whose fault it is.
But now you have a new family.
Don't lose your new family
because of the one that is no longer there.
However...
Do as you like.
To do as is best for me?
Yes, how better for the one you love
better for you too.
What about you then?
What is better for you?
What is best for you…
better for me too.
Sok Hune.
I have to talk to you.
is everything ok
are you hurt
Everything is fine.
Did you take painkillers?
I don't need them.
I feel great because I recharged.
It's time for us to get to work.
Mr. Chong
I heard you got hurt.
I saw in the news that you were attacked.
Don't believe everything you see in the news.
There they even accused an innocent woman of murder.
Let's go inside.
Run if you want to live.
Everyone around To To Hee dies.
Go beat him?
Even I can beat him to a pulp.
Ignore him.
I don't think Seok Hoon will be able to come.
Loyal supporter of To To Hee
will definitely not miss this meeting.
He must be planning to be late again.
Let's begin the special meeting of the board of directors.
Today we will vote for the applicants
to the position of chairman of "Mire Group".
I want to announce something.
Each candidate then
will have a chance to make a speech.
This is an important statement about voting.
OK, please.
To prevent further
conflicts and disputes,
I withdraw my candidacy.
What game has she started now?
We need to talk.
Then.
Then let's vote
whether to suggest Mr. No Suk Min
as the only candidate for the post of chairman
at the shareholders' meeting.
FOR, AGAINST, ABSENT
What are you doing in your own way?
Let's talk outside.
You made a difficult decision.
I appreciate it.
What game are you playing?
I decided to forgive and forget.
And I will refuse the inheritance.
So let's put an end to it
this war
I'm glad you finally did
made the right decision.
Well done.
Explain to me why you do this.
I am tired of all this.
Is this the thing?
I can no longer live on my nerves and in fear.
I can't even go by myself
to work or for a walk.
I want to live peacefully like everyone else
and return to normal life.
Therefore, I got rid of the reason,
from which I was hunted.
No.
you are lying
Look into my eyes.
And tell me the truth.
I can't trust you anymore.
What?
You can't protect me anymore.
You've become so weak
that you can't even protect yourself.
Are you satisfied with the answer?
No…
Why hasn't he come yet?
Why?
There is something wrong with his powers.
What is she thinking?
What will she do next?
This time she caught me by surprise.
Maybe she just gave up.
After all, she's too young
to cope with everything that fell on her.
As I have said many times,
she is not like that.
I'm sure she wants to
lull our vigilance
to stab us in the back.
Her bodyguard was recently attacked.
It probably scared her.
It can't be. She was not attacked.
She is not one to back down
even at gunpoint.
Whatever the reason, glad
that she understood her position
and gave up.
Great, dear.
He is not the head yet.
Isn't it too early for a toast?
Is that Kone?
- Thank you for the food.
- Sit until everyone has finished eating.
I have plans.
But To Kyone.
Sit back immediately.
Shall we continue?
Open the door, Director Jon!
Director Chong!
You can no longer protect me.
You have become so weak,
that you can't even protect yourself.
That is, you need him.
You lead him by the nose,
taking advantage of his weakness.
He almost died because of you.
What kind of egoist will you be?
Run if you want to live.
Everyone around To To Hee dies.
RESULTS OF THE SPECIAL MEETING
BOARD OF DIRECTORS OF "MIRE GROUP"
CEO NO SOOK MIN -
THE ONLY CANDIDATE FOR THE POSITION OF THE CHAIRMAN
I will give up, Seok Hoon.
I will withdraw my candidacy tomorrow.
To Hee
I did everything I could.
Ms. Chu would definitely understand.
Even if we catch the intruder,
it won't bring her back.
I think I just had to
to vent anger on something
after the loss of Ms. Chu.
Therefore, I could not leave it.
when i leave it
everyone will be happy.
You do it
for Mr. Chong's sake?
Because you don't want him to get hurt again?
I don't want to lose the one again
who is dear to me
You knew everything, right?
what happened
She definitely told you everything.
Why did she suddenly give up?
If you're so curious, ask her yourself.
She won't tell me anything!
didn't you tell me
that she has her own reasons for not telling?
You should have talked her out of it anyway.
You know how important it is to her
find Choo Jung Suk's killer?
I know that. I know it very well!
To Hee always
blamed herself for the death of her parents.
Now she will blame herself
and in the death of my aunt
through you!
What?
She gave up because of you.
I didn't want you to get hurt again.
To To Hee!
SAVIOR KU WON
All the flowers have fallen.
Ms. Chu.
you never saw
as your precious flowers bear fruit.
Are you really all right?
I'm sorry, Ms. Chu.
I'm so sorry.
Let's go back.
If you give up because of me
let's go back and fight again.
Everything is wrong.
To To Hee.
Do as you like.
Because it's better for me.
They are all dead.
Ms. Chu,
mom and dad
Everyone I loved in my life is dead.
And you will die too...
through me
I don't care.
Even if my feelings are for you
make me insignificant and weak,
you are my destiny,
which I cannot resist.
MY BELOVED DEMON
What is better for you
became what is best for me.
There is no way I will back down from To To Hee.
Man, ride me on your back.
I feel so free and happy.
Call yourselves Wild Dogs?
I have a task for you.
If you do not comply,
forbid you to appear before my eyes.
- Forward!
- Yes, detective?
- We found the culprit, Mrs. To.
His name is Ki Kwang Chul.
We are looking for him, so we will find him soon.
The game of hide and seek is over.
Clocks. They stopped.
My powers didn't just flicker.
They are completely gone.
Translation of subtitles: Daria Hochel